nice to meet you.
初めまして
It's so beautiful.
めちゃめちゃ綺麗だね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
This may be out of the blue, but I would like to ask you a few questions.
いきなりなんですけど、 いろいろちょっとお聞きしたいなと思
So, is it okay if I ask you a few questions?
って て、 何かいくつか質問しても大丈夫?
yes.
はい
What are you doing now?
今何してる人なの?
I'm a university student now.
今は大学生です
university student?
大学生?
He's a student.
学生さんだ
That's right.
そうなんだ
I'm a second year student now.
今は2年生
2nd year student.
2年生
I just got in.
入ったばっかなんだ
That's pretty much it.
まあまあそうだね
Is school fun?
学校楽しい?
結構
Is it fun?
楽しいか
I wish I could say it,
言えればいいんだけどさ、
Yeah.
うん
Is it okay to say that?
言 って大丈夫なの?
Well, well, well.
まあまあまあ
What were you studying?
どんなことを勉強してた?
For example, the department is plant nutrition.
例えば学科とかさ、 学科は植物栄養
Something like bioplant bio.
バイオプラントの バイオとか
I agree.
そうですね
plant-based.
植物系の
I don't know.
わかんない
I think you've adjusted it a little bit.
ちょっと合わせてくれたと思うんですけど、
I think he got into the groove,
ノリにね、合わせてくれたと思うんですけど、
I don't really understand.
よくわかんないんで
I'll let it flow.
流します
Right now, I'm quite a bit older than you, but...
今のさ、 俺結構年離れてるという あれなんだけど、
What do college students do for fun?
大学生って どんなことして遊んでるの?
What do you think?
どうだろう?
What is it?
なんだろう?
But what about karaoke?
でも、どうだろうな、 カラオケとか、
Because it's basic study, oh, what about basic study?
基本勉強だから、 あ、基本勉強は?
We'd go to Starbucks and study together.
スタバー行って、 みんなで勉強したりとか
I went to Starbucks, played UNO, and studied.
スタバー行って、 UNOして勉強して、
Do you play UNO at Starbucks?
スタバーでUNOとかする?
do not.
しない
Oh, why not?
あ、しない?
Do you have any club activities?
なんか部活とかやってるの?
My club activities were in high school, but I don't do them now.
部活は高校、 今はやってないけど、
When I was in high school.
高校の時に
Shall I guess?
当てよっか
Good boy.
いい子
It's really bittersweet.
めちゃめちゃ渋いですね
chess?
チェス?
I heard it for the first time.
初めて聞いた
To the cheer club.
チア部に
Cheer club?
チア部?
Chia.
チア
Oh, Chiaririn?
あ、チアリリンか
Chiarilin.
チアリリン
Cheer?
チア?
Ah, yes.
あ、いそう
It looks like a mess.
めちゃめちゃいそう
Looks like a lot of cheer.
めちゃめちゃチアにいそう
But at first she was a good girl.
でも最初はいい子って
Also.
また
Did you say that?
そんなこと言った?
I.
俺
What, did you say that?
え、言った?
I said it.
言いましたよ
It's Chia.
チアなんだわ
Does your high school have a club like that?
高校にそんな部活あるんだ?
I found out about it for the first time.
俺初めて知ったんだ
Cheering on high school baseball?
高校の 野球応援?
Cheering for high school baseball.
高校野球の 野球応援とか
I'll definitely watch it.
確かに見るわ
That's really a cheer squad.
あれって本当にチア部なんだ
Really chia.
本当にチア
I thought they were doing something.
なんか、 やってんのかと思った
Practice.
練習して
It looks like the cheerleading club is doing it.
チア部がやってんそうなんだ
The cheer team went to cheer them on.
チ ア部が応援しに行って
how was it?
どうだった?
it was fun?
楽しかった?
It was fun.
楽しかったですね
Try something now.
今ちょっと何かやってみて
Try something?
何かやってみて?
Chia, just give it a try.
チア、ちょっと やってみて
Try cheering.
チアやってみて
difficult.
難しい
Would you like to try cheerleading?
チアやってみてか
It seems like I can do it perfectly.
なんかパーっとできるような
Is it difficult now?
今難しいか
Is it difficult unless you are standing up?
基本立ってないと難しい?
There's nothing to support.
応援するものがないとね
Is that so?
そう かそうか
Do you have a part-time job?
バイトはしてる?
I have a part-time job.
バイトはしてます
At Misdo.
ミスドで
Missed?
ミスドか
This looks like it's going to be bad again.
これまたいそうだね
Looks like a stylish part-time job.
おしゃれなバイトっぽい
What do you like most about Misdo?
ミスドは何が一番好きなの?
Misdo is Pondering and Honey Churro.
ミスドは ポンデリングと ハニーチュロ
It's delicious.
うまいよね
delicious.
美味しい
I like honey churro the most.
ハニーチュロ一番好き
It's really delicious, isn't it?
めっちゃ美味しいですよね
It's seriously cute.
マジで可愛いね
Before that.
その 前に
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いじゃん
The style is really nice.
スタイルめちゃめちゃいいよね
I wonder what the style is.
スタイルは どうなんだろう
Because I was playing cheerleading.
チアやってたから
Honestly, I'm going off track, but that's about it.
正直さ、脱線しちゃうけどさ、 これぐらいのさ、
If you had an adopted child, wouldn't you be able to go into the entertainment industry?
養子持ってたらさ、 芸能界とか行けんじゃない?
Not interested?
興味ない?
Just a scout
一応 スカウト
Suddenly, I was walking on the street, feeling overwhelmed.
な の されて いきなり街で歩いてた
Seriously?
マジ?
It's been done.
されてるじゃん
Seriously?
マジ?
When was it done?
いつされたの?
I don't remember, but about when?
覚えてないけど だいたいいつぐらい?
I think it was during my first year.
1年生の時かな
That's right.
そうなんだ
picture?
え?
It's been done.
されてるじゃん
Don't you have anything to do?
やることないの?
I'm in an office for now.
一応事務所入ってる
I don't think he's really active like that right now.
今はそんな 本格的には 活動してないかな
As expected.
やっぱりですね
I agree.
そうだね
You're a second year student now, right?
今2年生でしょ?
Are you looking for a job next year?
来年就活かな?
Is it too early now?
今早まったのかな?
It's job hunting.
就活じゃん
Is there a job you want to do?
何かやりたい仕事かな?
Should I continue working full-fledgedly at the agency I currently belong to?
この今所属してる 事務所を そのまま本格的に 活動するか、
Are you looking for a job in the department you are currently studying?
今習ってる学科の 系統の 就職か、
I'm a little confused about whether to pursue a career in the entertainment industry.
芸能への道か ちょっと迷ってるかな
nice.
いいね
There definitely is.
絶対あるね
What a terrible future.
あかんような未来ね
If you go into the entertainment industry, if you get a certain amount of exposure.
もし さ、芸能の方に行ってさ、 もし ある程度露出してきたら
Can I support you?
さ、 応援していい?
No, I'm really happy.
いや、めちゃめちゃうれしい
I see?
なるほど?
Can I be your number one fan?
ファン第1号になっていい?
Please come and see us.
ぜひぜひ
Well, I'm a little off track, but I'd like to talk about something more specific.
じゃ、ちょっと脱線したけど、 一番具体的な話をしたい
The camera is rolling right now, right?
今カメラ回ってるでしょ?
What are you doing today?
今日はどんな事するんですか?
Today is...
今日は...
Well, that's what it is.
まあ、そういうことだよね
That's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいことだよね
Something like this
こういうの
Well, that's not normal, right?
って さ、 普通じゃないでしょ?
That's rare.
珍しいじゃん
why?
なんで?
You're a student, right?
学生さんでしょ?
Why did you come here?
なんでここに来たの?
With tuition...
学費で...
Tuition fees?
学費?
As for tuition fees, aren't there things like 2nd grade elementary school now?
学費ってさ、今小学2とかあるじゃん?
Can't you borrow it?
借りれないの?
I'm renting it, but
借りてるんだけど、
I lost quite a few units.
結 構単位落としちゃって
I have to pay my own tuition fees this year.
今年の学費は、 自分で払わないといけないから、
I just needed it.
ちょっと必要になっちゃって
In a hurry?
急遽か
I agree.
そうですね
destiny.
運命
That's it, isn't it?
あれですよね
for personal use
個人用で
I'm just taking pictures.
撮 ってるだけですよ
I think he wrote something like Twitter,
Twitterとかって書いてたと思うけど、
That's how it feels.
そう いう感じでね
This is a hobby for me.
僕は趣味なんですよ、これね
Because it's a hobby.
趣味だから
I guess it's just a hobby.
まあまあ趣味だからと いう感じだよね
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
Suddenly?
急に?
Are you feeling nervous?
緊 張してきた?
a little bit.
ちょっと
I see.
そっか
Go to the side to relieve your tension.
緊張をほぐすために、 横に行って
Really.
本当にね
Don't be so scared.
そんな怖がらないで
You don't get nervous, do you?
緊張しないでしょ
Wouldn't you be more nervous?
もっと緊張しないでしょ
Facing backwards.
後ろ向きでさ
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしい
ちょっと 恥ずかしい
Even today, I take pictures of various places near here.
今日でも、 この近くで、 いろんなとこ撮るよ
While making peace, make peace,
ピースしながら、 ピースしてさ、
I'll do my best to take some naughty pictures today while looking at the camera.
カメラ見ながらさ、 今日エッチな撮影頑張ります
do?
やる?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'll do it when I'm ready.
心の準備できたらやる
Because it begins.
始まるから
It will start when you go.
行ったら始まるんだよ
So I'll do it when I feel ready.
だから、自分の心の準備ができたらやる
When you're ready?
準備ができたら?
OK.
OKです
Today, I'll do my best to take naughty photos.
今日は、エッチな撮影頑張ります
Let's do our best.
頑張ろうね
Let's do our best, then.
頑張ろうか、じゃあ
I'm rooting for you.
応 援してるからね
Looks like an actress.
女優みたい
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いよ
め っちゃ可愛い
What do you think it starts with?
何から始まると思う?
From what?
何から?
As a manual pin.
手差しピンとして
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute?
ちょっと待つ?
Should I leave for once?
一回離れるかな?
Tell me when you're ready.
心の準備できて教えて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
恥 ず かしい
Draw a little face.
ちょっと顔を描いて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I quit.
やめた
Down, down.
下出して、下
Down?
下?
Are you taking pictures?
撮ってる?
Your hair is beautiful too.
髪も綺麗だね
Are you careful about your hair?
髪気をつけてるの?
what happened?
どうしたの?
I'm going to fall in love with you.
恋ぼとするんだよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Soft.
柔らか
How many cups?
何カップあんだ?
This is a D cup.
これDカップ
D cup?
Dカップ?
D's intentions are clear.
Dの意思ついてるんだ
Do you understand?
分かる?
D's intention.
Dの意思
Movies.
ムービーズ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm stretching my legs.
足伸ばしてる
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's too small.
ちっちゃくすぎる
Is it too hard?
く すぎる?
what up?
どうした?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Did you see something?
何か見えちゃったかな?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
dummy?
ダミー?
There's a drawing attached.
図面ついてるんだ
Time management.
時間対策
look
見
It's so hard, everything.
たい からさ、全部
You get it.
分かるよね
That means I stood up.
立ったってこと
Shall I take it off?
脱ごうか
It's so embarrassing.
下恥ずかしいな
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
This way?
こっち?
Yeah, below.
うん、下
Very
め っちゃ
The style is nice.
ス タイルいいじゃん
what up?
どうした?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
No?
ダメ?
Try stretching your legs.
足伸ばしてみてさ
Peace.
ピースして
It looks a lot like a commercial.
めっちゃCMっぽいよ
of a swimsuit.
水着の
There are often images of the ocean.
よく海の映像あるじゃん
Something like this in the beer.
ビールの中こんなやつ
It's really big.
めっちゃぽいよ
So good.
すげーいい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
So, just hold your elbows up there.
じゃあちょっとさ、そこにさ、 ひじついた状態を押してね
Do it like this.
こういうふうにしてね
What do you mean?
なんていうとこ?
Did you say that?
言うんでした?
clitoris?
クリトリス?
Does it feel good, clitoris?
気持ちいいの、クリトリス?
But where is the clitoris located?
でもさ、 クリトリスってさ、 どこについてるの?
So I was just touching here,
じゃあ今ここ触ってたけどさ、
I don't want to say it.
言 いたくない
Look at the camera.
カメラ見てって
カメラ見て
Do I have to say it?
言わなきゃダメ?
Isn't it good?
いいでしょ?
It's like this.
こんな感じでさ
Like this?
こんな感じで?
It's my first time.
初めてですね
Oh, I'm sorry.
あ、ごめんなさい
Because I don't.
し ないから
No?
ダメ?
The sides are a little...
脇はちょっと...
No armpit?
脇ダメ?
Side note, I'm running away.
脇、逃げてるんですよ
Damn that guy.
くそこったがいさんだ
You'll definitely run away, right?
絶対逃げるじゃないですか
No, I won't, I won't.
いや、しないしないしないよ
I'm too scared.
怖がりすぎる
Dudududu Dududu
ドゥドゥドゥドゥ ドゥドゥド
What should I do?
ゥ どう したらいいの?
It's not okay to touch it, right?
触ってダメなんでしょ?
Don't touch it.
触ってダメ
Because I don't touch it.
触らないから
Squiggly?
すぐったい?
sorry.
ごめんなさい
So there you have it, the fourth one.
じゃあ そこにさ、 手ついて4つ目なんだよ
Look here from the left.
左からこっち見て
Peace.
ピースして
piece?
ピース?
Write in emoji.
絵文字書き書きして
Why?
なんでって
Why are you hiding your hands?
なんで手を隠すの?
No.
ダメだよ
It was embarrassing.
恥ずかしかった
Suddenly.
急に
Was it embarrassing?
恥ずかしかった?
I was holding back though.
我慢してたけど
Shall we go to sleep?
寝ちゃおうか
The feeling is stuck.
気持ちしみついてる
No way.
やだ
It's ingrained.
しみついてる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
No way.
やだ
I say it makes me want to be mean.
意地悪したくなると言ってます
Just like before, make your hair white.
さっきと同じように 髪の毛を白にして
From the pin.
ピンから
Can I expand it myself?
自分で広げれる?
Is this better?
こっちのほうがいいですか?